[{"answer": "Oh, I think it's a little early to tell for sure.", "docId": "120606pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "What does it really mean in the bigger context of our election?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "I was asked by somebody if I thought that the current president was the weakest president, and I said I thought the competition probably was President Carter, that the two presidencies did not have the energy or the leadership.", "docId": "120606pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "Do you actually mean that?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "Well, it's a tough situation for the United States and for the administration.", "docId": "120606pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "What does America, what does President Obama actually do when you have great powers like Russia and China saying we're not playing ball?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "The idea that sanctions will work as long as Iran and Russia and other countries are supportive of the Assad regime is mindless.", "docId": "120606pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "If you were President Obama, what is the thing that you do to stop right now any more of these atrocities?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "Oh, I think probably the worst moment is being engaged in a war.", "docId": "120606pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "If I was to pin you down and say, what was your greatest moment in office and your worst moment, what would you say?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "Oh, I think any -- any person in tough jobs is so fortunate to have someone who can walk up to them and call them by their first name and tell them what they really think, and add some balance and perspective and dimension to a life that gets quite hectic sometimes when you're serving an important position.", "docId": "120606pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "How important is it to any political leader, do you think, to have that kind of person at their right-hand side?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Oh, goodness.", "docId": "120606pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "Do you think you've built up a reputation that is perhaps not entirely accurate?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "Well, I wouldn't -- it's not really surprising that the secretary would say something like that.", "docId": "120606pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "Your thoughts?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "There's nothing weird about flipping the state senate.", "docId": "120606pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "How are you claiming some kind of weird victory out of all this?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120606pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Are they all a bunch of mad extremists?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "ASSERMAN SCHULTZ: Yeah.", "docId": "120606pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "Were you choking on your soup?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120606pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "Was his opinion correct?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120606pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "And a big defeat for the Democrats, isn't it?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "MITH: I don't think so, because I think part of Romney's message is going to be about how he united both parties in Massachusetts, got things done as governor.", "docId": "120606pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Could Mitt Romney pick him as a VP?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "They are completely being disingenuous.", "docId": "120606pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "When the Democrats squeal about money, are they being disingenuous?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "I think you also have to remember that Donald Rumsfeld lost his job -- first job in the White House from the Ford administration to the Carter administration.", "docId": "120606pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "Completely.", "docId": "120606pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "Do you quibble?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "Let me stop you in full explosive flow.", "docId": "120606pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "If Iraq was a disaster, then what was Libya?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "Well, he actually increased the troop numbers in Afghanistan.", "docId": "120606pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "On the foreign policy stage, very hard to see many negatives, isn't it, for President Obama?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "I think Rumsfeld did have a point, that all of this talk of sanctions does not seem to be effective, that the choice Obama faces is whether or not to intervene militarily or not.", "docId": "120606pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "What do you think the smart thing for Obama to do is?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "I don't think you've seen any politicians, any sort of leading national politicians with a clear answer to that question.", "docId": "120606pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "Yet what do you do about the humanitarian catastrophe that is unfurling before our eyes?", "qSentId": 444}]